<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><operatorModel xmlns="http://www.ibm.com/xmlns/prod/streams/spl/operator" xmlns:cmn="http://www.ibm.com/xmlns/prod/streams/spl/common" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.ibm.com/xmlns/prod/streams/spl/operator operatorModel.xsd">
  <!--DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - it is machine generated-->
  <javaOperatorModel>
    <!--Generated from com.ibm.streamsx.json.JSONToTuple in impl/lib/com.ibm.streamsx.json.jar at Thu Mar 26 16:11:10 EDT 2015-->
    <context>
      <description>This operator converts JSON strings into SPL Tuples. The tuple structure is expected to match the JSON schema. A subset of the attributes can be specified as well.  Only those attributes that are present in the Tuple schema and JSON input will be converted. All other attributes will be ignored. If an invalid JSON string is found in the input, the operator will fail.  This behavior can be overridden by specifying the optional output port or by specifying the "ignoreParsingError" parameter. Atributes from the input stream that match those in the output stream will be automaticall copied over.  However, if they also exist in the JSON input, their assigned value will be of that specified in the JSON. Null values in JSON arrays are ignored. Null values for all other attributes will result in default initializled output attributes.  Limitations: BLOB, MAP and COMPLEX attribute types are not supported in the output tuple schema at this time and will be ignored.</description>
      <metrics/>
      <executionSettings>
        <className>com.ibm.streamsx.json.JSONToTuple</className>
      </executionSettings>
      <libraryDependencies>
        <library>
          <cmn:description>Operator class library</cmn:description>
          <cmn:managedLibrary>
            <cmn:libPath>../../impl/lib/com.ibm.streamsx.json.jar</cmn:libPath>
            <cmn:libPath>@STREAMS_INSTALL@/ext/lib/JSON4J.jar</cmn:libPath>
          </cmn:managedLibrary>
        </library>
      </libraryDependencies>
    </context>
    <parameters>
      <parameter>
        <name>ignoreParsingError</name>
        <description>Ignore any JSON parsing errors.If the optional output port is enabled, then this parameter is ignored. JSON that cannot be parsed is sent on the optional output port. Default is false where the operator will fail if the JSON cannot be parsed.</description>
        <optional>true</optional>
        <type>boolean</type>
        <cardinality>1</cardinality>
      </parameter>
      <parameter>
        <name>jsonStringAttribute</name>
        <description>Name of the input stream attribute which contains the JSON string. This attribute must be of USTRING or RSTRING type. Default is jsonString</description>
        <optional>true</optional>
        <type>rstring</type>
        <cardinality>1</cardinality>
      </parameter>
      <parameter>
        <name>jsonStringOutputAttribute</name>
        <description>Name of the output stream attribute which should be populated with the incoming JSON string. This attribute must be of USTRING or RSTRING type. Default is to ignore.</description>
        <optional>true</optional>
        <type>rstring</type>
        <cardinality>1</cardinality>
      </parameter>
      <parameter>
        <name>targetAttribute</name>
        <description>Name of the output stream attribute which should be considered as the root of the JSON tuple to be populated. Note that this can only point to a tuple type or collection type attributes (list, set etc). If it points to a list, set etc type attribute, the input JSON is expected to be an array. Default is the output tuple root.</description>
        <optional>true</optional>
        <type>rstring</type>
        <cardinality>1</cardinality>
      </parameter>
    </parameters>
    <inputPorts>
      <inputPortSet>
        <description/>
        <windowingDescription/>
        <windowingMode>NonWindowed</windowingMode>
        <windowPunctuationInputMode>Oblivious</windowPunctuationInputMode>
        <controlPort>false</controlPort>
        <cardinality>1</cardinality>
        <optional>false</optional>
      </inputPortSet>
    </inputPorts>
    <outputPorts>
      <outputPortSet>
        <description/>
        <windowPunctuationOutputMode>Free</windowPunctuationOutputMode>
        <cardinality>1</cardinality>
        <optional>false</optional>
      </outputPortSet>
      <outputPortSet>
        <description/>
        <windowPunctuationOutputMode>Free</windowPunctuationOutputMode>
        <cardinality>1</cardinality>
        <optional>true</optional>
      </outputPortSet>
    </outputPorts>
  </javaOperatorModel>
</operatorModel>